May! Hang in there!
Thanks, Cecil.
Grant me the power I seek...
Hinata! You have to end this now!
Leave it to me, Bell!
That light...
Demon Lord!
This is where you DIE!
Hero—!
Hinata did it!
That's our hero!
Peace will return to the land at last...
Huh?
Hinata, what's happening?!
Guess it's time to go.
I was summoned from another world
to defeat the Demon Lord.
Now that I've done my job, I have to leave.
What?!
No!
But... But then...
What about our promise to get married
once we defeated the Demon Lord?!
Huh...?
Not again...
Well, I don't think that's...
Just because you've been
saying that since we met...
Why not?! Do you hate me or something?!
No, it's not that...
Then marry me!
Marry me! Marry me! Marry me!
A female dark elf named Mariabell.
I met her in another world, and...
she's slightly obsessed with me...
I don't have much longer...
No! If you disappear, Hinata, then I...
Don't make this difficult for Lord Hinata.
Cecil...
She's right!
Let's see him off with a smile!
May...
But...
Don't cry, Bell.
It makes me sad that
I have to leave you guys...
but we'll meet again someday.
Okay...
Bye, everyone! Until next time!
Bye-bye!
Take care.
Goodbye, Hinata!
I swear I'll find a way—
I'm heading out.
It's been a month since I returned
from another world.
This will be on the test!
Things have gone completely back to normal.
A safe and peaceful daily life,
just like I wanted.
But...
Bye!
Later!
S-Sunohara?
U-Um, I...
Sakura, we're leaving!
Oh, okay!
See you tomorrow...
'Kay. See ya, Mochida.
Good thing I got to buy
a bunch of stuff on sale today.
I'm home—
Never mind...
There's no one here anyway.
What's that...?
HI-NA-TA!
Wha—?! Wait...
Hinata!
B-Bell?! How did—
Hinata! Hinata! Hinata! Hinata! Hinata!
Did you miss me while I was gone?!
You missed me, right?!
I missed you so much,
I thought I was gonna go crazy!
But everything's okay now.
I'll never let you be all by yourself!
If anything, we ought to grow
the fruits of our love.
How many children do you want?
Bell, lemme breathe for a sec!
Oh, how dominant of you!
N-No, wait...!
This is perfect.
I knew you'd want to do it right away.
I'm ready whenever you are.
Calm down!
A-And please put some clothes on!
I'm surprised you came alone.
I've heard that it takes many mages
and many years to pull off
traveling between worlds.
Smells like Hinata!
What are you doing...?
Indeed, it wasn't easy.
But it didn't matter
because I wanted to see you.
Peace returned to our world,
and everyone touted us as saviors...
But it all seemed so boring to me.
I felt an awful emptiness inside.
This life means nothing to me
without you in it.
As long as I've got you, I'm happy.
You're the only thing I need.
I won't allow anything to stand
in the way of the love we share.
Whether it's demon lords or
alternate dimensions,
I'd tear it all down just to reach you.
I'll be by your side for all eternity.
Hinata?
Yeah...?
Hinata...
Sh-She's... intense.
Hinata, I can't take it any longer!
B-Bell?! What's with you all of a sudden?!
Well, I guess "sudden" isn't
the right word, but I still—
Huh?
I used up all my strength
and magic to get here...
I'm exhausted...
Tasty!
Good.
It's food from my world,
so I wasn't sure if you'd like it.
It's totally fine!
After all, you're the one who made it.
Been a while since I last sat down
to eat with Bell like this...
Having someone to share my meals with
makes me really happy.
Despite things being peaceful and
safe here, it's felt like living in a fog.
But when Bell appeared in my room,
that fog vanished all at once.
Thanks, Bell.
I'm glad you came to visit me.
That's my line, silly.
I'm the one who's glad to see you.
Remember what I said earlier?
I'll always be by your side, Hinata.
Earlier...
Always?
Bell, does that mean you
want to live here?
Of course! You just figured that out?
Oh, right...
Aw, don't worry, Hinata!
I'll help out around the house!
And you can't say no if I've already
made my decision!
Bell, you said the quiet part out loud...
Well, at any rate...
Let's see... This hand goes here...
"I'm brand new to this, but I hope
you'll take good care of me."
Hey! Why are you laughing?!
M-My bad!
You caught me off guard, that's all...
I heard it's what the people here say
before getting married!
I practiced and everything!
Oof, I'm full.
I could go for a nice hot bath
right around now.
Go ahead, and take your time.
But you have to come with me, Hinata.
Huh?
I don't know how bathtubs work
in your world.
So, you had better hop in, too.
I-I mean, I can just show you...
C'mon, Hinata. Please?
Fine...
Too hot? Is it okay?
It's perfect. That feels fantastic.
Wow...
It's so sleek and smooth,
and I haven't even put anything in it.
It slips through my fingers like silk.
I'm very proud of my hair.
I get it from my mom.
In the other world, a dark elf's black hair
and tanned skin are said to be an ill omen...
but I find that hard to believe.
It's so beautiful, and shiny.
Like the full moon in the night sky.
Jeez, kinda cheesy, don't you think?
Sorry! I just...
You're the same as ever...
Nobody's allowed to touch it
except for you, Hinata.
You do know you're special to me, right?
Y-Yeah... I'll start washing it now.
Mm, that smells lovely.
There are all sorts of haircare products.
Should we go shopping
in town sometime soon?
Sounds good.
I guess it didn't need any conditioner...
Thank you.
Okay, now it's my turn to wash yours!
H-Huh?! No, I can do it—
Don't be shy!
I'll scour every inch of your body
for any built-up dirt or grime,
and then I'll squeeze
every last drop out of you.
What do you mean by "squeeze"?!
Aw, you're sweating.
We had better get you all cleaned up...
I feel woozy...
Gonna fall...
What happened?! Did you get lightheaded?!
P-Please, Bell...
I can't take much more...
It's your fault, y'know.
If you look at me like that,
I won't be able to hold back any longer...
Oh my...
You are in the mood, aren't you, Hinata?
Then I'll help myself...
No! Please, no more!
Hinata, wait—!
Hinata, stay with me!
Oh, Hinata. You're awake?
Are you in pain?
I'm sorry, Hinata. I shouldn't have
gotten carried away...
No, I should've paid more attention.
It wasn't your fault, Bell.
Hinata...
I like your hair, too.
Mine?
Mm-hmm! It's all fluffy...
and warm and toasty...
It reminds me of sunlight.
Th-Thanks...
Hey, Hinata?
Earlier, you compared my hair
to the night sky...
but without the Sun,
the Moon can't shine on its own.
Bell...
So, y'see... That's why I can never,
ever, EVER let you go.
R-Right...
If I were to lose you again, Hinata...
well, I don't know what I'd do.
'Kay?
A female dark elf named Mariabell.
I met her in another world, and...
she's slightly obsessed with me...
But she's a very pure-hearted girl,
and very cute.